Make a cup of coffee and since we are more than a thousand subscribers now we will celebrate with a small bun
I haven't paid for so #sparadkrona
Before I have eaten my bun, I will also present the winners and the winners that I pulled is
Filip Rydin
Emil Hanna upstream Siberia's soup kitchen
Åsa Lundgren Hurry nurse Karam Julia and Ardalan
Congratulations You have won each share book You can contact me on Instagram or Facebook
With your address so I send out the books to you
In today's video so we'll talk about
Shares or funds, ie
What should you choose
When you invest and save your money
so do you have to think about how much risk you are willing to take
By investing in shares so take very high risk
And when you invest in equity funds, there is also a high risk but not as high as if you had only bought 1 share
So if that company goes bad (in which you bought shares)
so does your entire investment go to the beep turn
But if you buy a fund instead
Then you spread out the risk
Among different companies
At least 16 shares you get if you buy a fund
I usually say that